uninor.in 2012-05-29

# Privacy Policy: Uninor India

Unitech Wireless (Tamilnadu) Private Limited, (referred to as "Uninor") is committed to protecting your Personal Information and/or Sensitive Personal Data or Information. We have created this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we handle and deal with above referred information when you visit Uninor web /WAP sites and/or use our products and services.

This Privacy policy covers the following:

  1. Collection of Personal Information including Sensitive personal Data or Information.
  2. Use of your Personal Information.
  3. Disclosure of Personal Information.
  4. Protection of your Personal Information.
  5. Review and updation of Personal Information.
  6. Changes to our Privacy Policy.
  7. Definitions used in this policy.

####  1\.    Collection of Personal Information including Sensitive Personal Data or Information

We and our authorized third parties may collect different types of Personal Information and Sensitive personal Data Or Information, as required under laws and regulation and also based on your use of our products and services and our business relationship with you.

This Personal Information collected, handled and dealt by us may include, amongst other things,

**Subscription Information** that allows Uninor to provision desired services and to communicate with you and comply with current legal and regulatory requirements. This information may include without limitation:

a.   Your name, address, telephone numbers, email id, photographs. 

b.   Information contained in documents used as proof of Identity and proof of address. 

**Service Information** such as service or complaint history, email or letter sent by you, payment history etc. **Equipment, performance, and other technical information** which gets generated during your use of our network, services and products such as call detail records, usage analysis, location information, IP addresses assigned, signaling information, network related information and any other information collected automatically in relation to your use of Uninor web/wap site, products and services by our equipment and systems. 

Other Information may be collected in form of various surveys which you agree to participate in or provide other feedback to us regarding our products or services; when you register to receive news or public policy updates or when you apply for a job through our website; subscription enquires through our web site. 

**Sensitive Personal Data Or Information** may be received, stored and processed by us or our authorized third parties such as passwords, financial information such as bank accounts or other payment instruments details for providing or products, services. 

In case you do not provide your information or consent for usage of personal information or later on withdraw your consent for usage of the personal information so collected, Uninor reserves the right to discontinue the services for which the said information was sought. In case you do not provide your information or consent for usage of personal information or later on withdraw your consent for usage of the personal information so collected, Uninor reserves the right to discontinue the services for which the said information was sought.

####  2\.    Use of your Personal Information.

The Personal Information that we collect from you is held in accordance with applicable laws and regulations in India. It may be used by us for a number of lawful purposes connected with our business operations and functions, which include but not limited to: 

a) Verification of your identity as per prevalent laws and regulation;

b) processing your request and providing you with products and/or services requested or administering your account; 

c) settling accounts with those who provide related services to us; 

d) dealing with requests, enquiries or complaints and other customer care related activities; and all other general administrative and business purposes; 

e) Carrying out market and product analysis and marketing our companies’ products and services and communicate updates, offers and promotion.

f) Customer analytics on usage pattern and deliver customized content and advertising that may be of interest to you;

g) Provide you with the best customer experience possible;

h) Address network integrity and security issues;

i) Your location information may be used to provide you with differentiated services such as dynamic pricing, location based services and/or comply to legal and regulatory requirements;

j) carrying out any activity in connection with a legal, governmental or regulatory requirement , for the purpose of compliance of a legal obligation, in connection with legal proceedings, in connection with prevention, detection , investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution, and punishment of offences protect and defend our rights or property or act in an emergency to protect someone's safety or to help investigations, monitor or prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person.

k) Carrying out activities connected with the running of our business such as personnel training, quality control, network monitoring, testing and maintenance of computer and other systems and in connection with the transfer of any part of our business in respect of which you are a customer or a potential customer;

####  3\.    Disclosure of Personal Information.

We may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information at times to third parties in cases it is necessary for providing services to you and/or if you have consented for the same. We may disclose and/or transfer your information to: 

a) Other communications companies as a normal part of our business for connecting and charging of calls over each other’s networks.

b) other companies that provide services directly to you on our behalf or provide services to us by collecting, receiving ,processing, storing, dealing or handling your information. To enable them to do this, we may need to share your personal information with them. 

c) anyone we transfer our business to in respect of which you are a customer or a potential customer; 

d) to any other entity or organization in order for them to understand our environment and consequently, provide you with better services.

We may obtain your consent for sharing your Sensitive Personal Data or Information in several ways, such as in writing; online, through "click-through" agreements; orally, including through interactive voice response; or when your consent is part of the terms and conditions pursuant to which we provide you services.

We may share your Personal Information including Sensitive personal Data or Information, without obtaining your prior written consent, with government agencies mandated under the law to obtain information including Sensitive Personal Data Or Information for the purpose of verification of identity, or for prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution, and punishment of offences, or where disclosure is necessary for compliance of a legal obligation.

Any Personal Information including Sensitive Personal Data Or Information may be required to be disclosed to any third party by us by an order under the law for the time being in force.

####  4\.    Protection of your Personal Information 

We shall take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information pertaining to you is stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

  * We maintain information pertaining to you in our business records as per current regulatory requirements. 
  * Uninor has comprehensive documented information security policy and procedures in line with international standard IS/ISO/IES 27001 to ensure that the information provided by you is reasonably secure.
  * Uninor shall retain your personal Information for as long as required to provide you with services or otherwise required under the law. 

In case of any privacy related concerns, feedback or grievance , you can contact your respective circle Grievance officer/ Nodal officer or Appellate Authority of which details have been provided in link below:

**Grievance officer**  

####  5\.    Review and updation of Personal Information.

We strive to keep our records updated with your latest information. To this end, if you see any discrepancy in your personal information or if a part of your personal information changes, we request you to visit UNINOR stores or reach our customer service at 121 or write to us at [care@uninor.in.](mailto:care@uninor.in)

####  6\.    Changes to our Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to update this Policy as necessary from time to time. Please check our websites periodically for changes to this Privacy Policy.

####  7\.    Definitions used in this policy 

**“Personal information”** means any information that relates to a natural person, which, either directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available with a body corporate, is capable of identifying such person

**“Sensitive personal data or information”** of a person means such personal information which consists of information relating to:-

i. password; 

ii. financial information such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details ; 

iii.physical, physiological and mental health condition; 

iv. sexual orientation; 

v. medical records and history; 

vi. Biometric information; 

provided that, any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force shall not be regarded as sensitive personal data or information for the purposes of these rules.

**Third party:** For the purposes of this document, a ‘Third Party’ is a service provider who associates with Uninor and is involved in handling, managing, storing, processing, protecting and transmitting information of Uninor and also includes all sub-contractors, consultants and/or representatives of the Third party.
